<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CovidHQ</string>

    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_general_guidelines">General Guidelines</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Allopathy</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Siddha</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Ayurveda</string>
    <string name="general_guidelines">
        Some General Guidelines like:\n\n
        &#8226; Wash hands using soap/handwash regularly.\n\n
        &#8226; Use handrubs and sanitizers during unavailability of soap and water.\n\n
        &#8226; Wear masks all the time.\n\n
        &#8226; Maintain Social distancing by staying atleast 6 feet apart from others.\n\n
        &#8226; Donot share your accessories with others.\n\n
        &#8226; Avoid crowdy places and poorly ventilated areas.\n\n
        &#8226; Get vaccinated if you get a chance.\n\n
        &#8226; Take medicines and treatment with doctors advice.\n\n
        &#8226; If possible have a caretaker for help.\n\n
        &#8226; Do breathing exercises and Yoga for mental and physical wellness.\n\n
        &#8226; Donot watch News or current COVID case updates, as they may increase stress.\n\n
        &#8226; Check your symptoms every day.\n\n
        &#8226; Be aware of your circumstances and donot believe on fake news.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="siddha_medications_1">
        &#8226; Herbal water infusion made up of half teasppon of Chukku(Dried Ginger) boiled in 2 litres of water can be used as drinking water.\n\n
        &#8226; Steam inhalation with Tulasi, Nochi leaves, Turmeric can be taken twice a day.\n\n
        &#8226; Water boiled with a pinch of salt and turmeric should be gargled atleast 3 times a day.\n\n
        &#8226; Neem leaves fumigation can be done to sanitise the quarantine environment.\n\n
        &#8226; Some anti-viral formulations and herbs:\n\n


    </string>

    <string name="tabbed_siddha_medication">
        &#8226; Kabasura Kudineer - 60ml twice a day after food\n\n
        &#8226; Nilavembu Kudineer - 60ml twice a day after food\n\n
        &#8226; Inji Surasam - 10ml once a day\n\n
        &#8226; Karunjeeraga Chooranam - 1gm BD\n\n
        &#8226; Musumusukai Adai - Can be taken as food item.\n\n
        &#8226; Nellikai Ilagam - 2 to 4gm twice a day\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="siddha_medication_2">
        Since the dose recommendations may differ according to age group and health conditions, Consult
        qualified Siddha Practitioner before taking the medicines.\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="allopathy_medication">
        <ul>
            &#8226; Be in Communication with a treating Doctor and report in case of any complications.\n\n
            &#8226; Take steam inhalation and warm water gargles twice a day.\n\n
            &#8226; For mild fever, take Tab. Paracetamol 650mg tablets four times a day.\n\n
            &#8226; If fever still persists, consult your Doctor, who may prescribe non-steroidal anti-inflammatory
            drugs (NSAID) like Tab. Naproxen 250mg twice a day.\n\n
            &#8226; Tab. Ivermectin 200mcg/kg can be taken once a day, in empty stomach for 3 to 5 days.\n\n
            &#8226; If you have mild symptoms beyond 5 days, consult your Doctor for treatment with Inhalational Budesonide via inhalers
            with spacer at a dose of 800mcg twice daily for 5 to 7 days.\n\n
            &#8226; If symptoms persist beyond 7 days, consult the treating doctor for treatment with low dose oral steroids.\n\n
            &#8226; <b>Donot take Remdesivir medicine at home without the advice of your treating doctor or help of a Medical Professional.</b>\n\n
            &#8226; In case of high symptoms like breathing difficulty or failing of Oxygen Levels, get admitted in a hospital
            immediately.\n\n
            &#8226; If 10 days have passed after symptoms and no fever for 3 days, you can discontinue your Home Quarantine.
            But Still, Stay Home. Stay Safe.\n\n
        </ul>
    </string>

    <string name="ayurveda_medication_1">
        &#8226; Use the medicines with caution and consult a qualified physician before having any medicine.\n\n
        &#8226; If you are already taking any medication for other health issues like diabetes, hypertension,
        cancer-chemotherapy etc., you can continue them with the physician consultation.\n\n
        &#8226; Instead of Tea, Drink warm water boiled with medicinal herbs like Trikatu, Cinnamon,
        Tulsi Leaves, Ashwagandha Root Powder etc.\n\n
        &#8226; For mild symptoms like Fever, Sore Throat, Cough and Dehydration, you can take any
        of the following medicines:\n\n

     </string>


    <string name="tabbed_ayurveda_medication">
         &#8226; Amritarista 15-20ml tid with water after food\n\n
         &#8226; Bilwadivati 1 TDS\n\n
         &#8226; Guduchyadi Kashayam freshly prepared 30-40ml BD before food\n\n
         &#8226; Haridra Khanda 3-5gm BD with lukewarm water or milk\n\n
         &#8226; Talisadi Churna 4g + Madhuyashtichurna 2g BD with honey/lukewarm water\n\n
         &#8226; Shadangapaneeya 40ml tid\n\n
        &#8226; For high symptoms like breathing difficulty, you can take any of the following medicines:\n\n
         &#8226; Inhalation with Karpoora and Nilgiritaila\n\n
         &#8226; Pushkaramoolasava 15-20ml TDS with equal water\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="ayurveda_medication_2">
           &#8226; Include spices like Cardamom, Dry ginger, Black pepper and garlic, Vegetables like
            brinjal, Bitter gourd and Drumstick, Fruits such as Grapes, Kapittha(Wood Apple Extract),
            Pomegranate, in your diet.\n\n
        &#8226; Restrict use of sweet, chilled, fried, oily food items, which is heavy to digest.\n\n
        &#8226; Practice Yogasana and Pranayama for atleast 30 minutes.\n\n
        &#8226; Children below 15 years of age, Pregnant/Lactating women should strictly take advice from the Physician to use
        the medications.\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_medicines">Medications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_medications">Medications</string>


    <string name="booki">BookI</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="read_it_together">Read it together</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget Password.?</string>


    <string name="calories">

        &#8226; Non-obese -25-30kcal/kg Actual Body Weight\n
        &#8226; Overweight or obese- 25-30kcal/kg IBW or Adjusted BW\n
        &#8226; Underweight -25-35kcal/kg Adjusted BW\n
        &#8226; Protein requirement – 1-1.5gm/kg/ Actual Body Weight\n
        &#8226; Fats requirement – 25-30% of the total calories\n
        &#8226; Multivitamin, minerals &amp; trace elementsVitamin D – 10-1000mcg/day\n
        &#8226; Vitamin A – to be consumed through diet\n
        &#8226; Vitamin E – 134-800mg/day\n
        &#8226; Zinc – 30-220mg\n
        &#8226; Vitamin C – 200mg- 2gm\n

    </string>

    <string name="ons">

        &#8226; Around 400-600kcals/day and 30gms of protein should be provided through ONS. This should be continued for at least a month.\n
        &#8226; Assessment should be done every 3rd day for patients.\n

    </string>

    <string name="covidguidelinesnutrition">

        &#8226; Leftover food to be treated as medical waste.\n
        &#8226; Regular physical activity and breathing exercise to be advised, as per tolerance.\n
        &#8226; Having a balanced diet with moderate carbs and fats, and High Biological Value proteins.\n
        &#8226; Provide Oral Nutrition Supplements and Antioxidants to meet the demands of the patients.\n
        &#8226; Consumption of Antioxidant Vitamins and Minerals should be encouraged especially Vitamin C and Vitamin D.\n

    </string>




</resources>
